<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wolf Suite</title>
    <link>https://wolf-suite.web.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wolf Suite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:23:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wolf-suite.web.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Tags 1.2.0 Update</title>
      <link>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/wolf-tags-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/wolf-tags-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Wolf Tags has received an update!
Note: These features may take up to an hour to appear in your server. Please be patient while Discord updates the commands.
Tag Command Mentions Users Now, you can use the /tag command to mention a user with a tag. Very useful for those who don&amp;rsquo;t read.
Taginfo Content Can be Copied The /taginfo command now uses backticks to allow for easy copying.
Boring Developer Stuff  README file on GitHub repository now shows installation instructions, along with license information and a prettier image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Tags 1.1.0 Update</title>
      <link>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/wolf-tags-1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:08:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/wolf-tags-1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Wolf Tags has received a small update bringing one new feature and a bug fix.
Note: These features may take up to an hour to appear in your server. This is due to the nature of Discord slash commands. Please be patient.
&amp;ldquo;previewtag&amp;rdquo; Command Now, you can use the /previewtag command to view a tag&amp;rsquo;s contents without showing the entire server. Just use the command like the /tag command.
Activity is No Longer Shown Instead of using an activity (ex: &amp;ldquo;Playing (random website)&amp;quot;), Wolf Tags will now use the description for linking to the bot website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WolfieCBOT ESR End of Life</title>
      <link>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/wolfiecbot-esr-eol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 18:55:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/wolfiecbot-esr-eol/</guid>
      <description>For those who did not know already, WolfieCBOT ESR will be shutting down on April 30th, 2022.
FAQ Why are you shutting WolfieCBOT ESR down?  WolfieCBOT ESR is not used in many servers. There are security issues with WolfieCBOT ESR that are unpatchable without completely rewriting the bot. Many of the features of WolfieCBOT ESR are locked down (ex: Moderation, Tags, etc.). Many of the features of WolfieCBOT ESR are being replicated with other Wolf Suite bots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site</title>
      <link>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 23:36:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolf-suite.web.app/blog/new-site/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our new site! We are excited to launch this site using the Portio theme and Hugo. We hope that this website will provide lots of information for our users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolf Tags</title>
      <link>https://wolf-suite.web.app/bots/wolf-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wolf-suite.web.app/bots/wolf-tags/</guid>
      <description>Storing your information has never been easier. With Wolf Tags, you can store your information bits with ease. Simply use the /createtag command.
Made a mistake? Change it. With the /edittag command, you never have to worry about messing up your information. Be assured that only you can modify your tags.
Made too many tags? Delete them. With the /deletetag command, you can easily remove any tag you own. You can also delete them as long as you can Manage Messages, making moderation a breeze.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>